bluegolf.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy

BlueGolf, LLC. and its related companies ("BlueGolf") recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of Personal Information collected about its Users. "Personal Information" includes, but is not limited to, usage data, along with the name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and credit card and salary information of BlueGolf Users. Therefore, BlueGolf does not sell or otherwise disclose any Personal Information. Nor does BlueGolf include in BlueGolf any functionality for performing "reverse searches" to identify BlueGolf Users from their e-mail addresses. However, BlueGolf reserves the right to analyze and utilize User data in order to more effectively optimize the User experience and to present certain opportunities to Users for their benefit. BlueGolf has adopted this Privacy Policy to inform BlueGolf Users how it does collect, store, and use Personal Information. BlueGolf's intent is to balance its legitimate business interests in collecting and using Personal Information against the reasonable expectations of privacy of its Users.   

  1. **Collection**  
BlueGolf collects Personal Information during e-mail and site registration, store purchases, and other user registration processes. In addition, BlueGolf collects Personal Information from BlueGolf Users in the form of usage data (for example, length of session, pages viewed, etc.) for use as provided in paragraph 3 below. 
  2. **Cookies**  
"Cookies" are pieces of information that BlueGolf transfers to the hard drives of BlueGolf Users for record-keeping purposes. BlueGolf places Cookies with BlueGolf Users visiting from advertising banners and hyperlinks on other websites to track the success of a particular advertising campaign or marketing program. In addition, BlueGolf places Cookies with BlueGolf Users to provide them with seamless access to BlueGolf, since storing their user name and password in a Cookie eliminates the need to reenter that information on every page. (Note: Browsers set to provide notice when a Cookie is placed will prompt BlueGolf Users to accept or reject the Cookie.) The use of Cookies is an industry standard and occurs at most major websites. 
  3. **Usage**   
BlueGolf uses Personal Information for: developing enhancements to BlueGolf; marketing and promotional purposes (for example, offering BlueGolf Users the opportunity to take advantage of special promotions and acquire BlueGolf products); and evaluating BlueGolf usage by analyzing usage data in the aggregate, but not with respect to any individual BlueGolf User. 

In addition, BlueGolf uses Personal Information to direct e-mail to BlueGolf Users who provide their e-mail address in connection with specific promotions (for example, receiving notice of winning a BlueGolf contest), or to direct e-mail regarding BlueGolf updates and service enhancements to Users who opt in either during the BlueGolf registration process or afterwards. 

  4. **Third Parties**  
BlueGolf may provide demographic information in the aggregate regarding BlueGolf Users to third parties in connection with BlueGolf advertising campaigns and marketing programs; however, no Personal Information relating to any individual BlueGolf User is disclosed. The only exception to this is if a User purchases an item at our online Store and we are using a commerce partner to fulfill orders for that particular item. In the event that sharing personal information is necessary under those circumstances, we only disclose that which is required to deliver your order. No credit card information is disclosed. 
  5. **Children**  
Children should always ask parents for permission before providing any Personal Information to BlueGolf or purchasing any products or services from BlueGolf. 
  6. **Security**  
BlueGolf only collects Personal Information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve its legitimate business purposes, and it uses state-of-the-art security technology to ensure the security, integrity, and privacy of all Personal Information. In addition, BlueGolf uses security measures in connection with the collection and transmission of Personal Information during the BlueGolf registration process. Nonetheless, BlueGolf is not responsible for any breach of its security or for the actions of any third parties that may obtain any Personal Information. 
  7. **Removal or Update of Personal Information**  
BlueGolf Users may update their Personal Information or remove their Personal Information from BlueGolf distribution lists via any of the means listed below. Please be sure to include the following information in your correspondence: 

BlueGolf complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. BlueGolf has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>. 

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, BlueGolf commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact BlueGolf directly at: [privacy@bluegolf.com](mailto:privacy@bluegolf.com). 

BlueGolf has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning data transferred from the EU. 

Privacy Shield Policy
